<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Afternoons on Software Architecture Forum: A Self-Organizing Open Spaces Conference in Crested Butte, Colorado Sept 25 - 29, 2017</title>
    <link>http://softwarearchitectureforum.com/afternoon/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Afternoons on Software Architecture Forum: A Self-Organizing Open Spaces Conference in Crested Butte, Colorado Sept 25 - 29, 2017</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://softwarearchitectureforum.com/afternoon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Activities</title>
      <link>http://softwarearchitectureforum.com/afternoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://softwarearchitectureforum.com/afternoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During conference days (Monday, Tuesday, Thursday and Friday), the afternoons
are unscheduled time. There are numerous options. Note that, although some of
these look like pure recreation, we have some of our most interesting
discussions once the structure and constraints are completely removed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Small hikes to experience the outdoors&lt;/strong&gt;. I generally start with a very easy one
around Lake Irwin, which is a relatively flat walk around a beautiful lake. This
is good for people who are getting used to the altitude and to test your endurance.
If this is easy, then you&amp;rsquo;re ready for subsequent days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mountain biking&lt;/strong&gt;. For beginners there&amp;rsquo;s an easy trail I take people on
later in the week. Other attendees who are more experienced bikers may offer
trips earlier in the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fishing and river rafting&lt;/strong&gt;. These trips can be arranged through services
available in town.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Workshops&lt;/strong&gt;. People often spontanously decide to create their
own workshops to investigate a particular idea or technology. Rooms at the
Parish Hall are usually available, or you can hold them at one of the rental
houses or in my living room (which has a Chromcast-enable TV).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rest and Recovery&lt;/strong&gt;. In case you need rest to get used to the altitude, or
to work on your own, or just recover from life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>